goboom4i.com 2011-06-05

# Privacy Policy | GoBoom.search4i.com Social Bookmarking | GoBoom It

## PRIVACY POLICY

What information do we collect?  
We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.  
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.  
Like most websites, we use cookies and/or web beacons to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the 'do we use cookies?' section below for information about cookies and how we use them.  

What do we use your information for?  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  
• To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)  
• To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)  
• To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)  
• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature  

How do we protect your information?  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information.

Do we use cookies?  
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.  
We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.  
If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting customer service.  

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.   
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.  

Third party links  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.  

Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.  

Online Privacy Policy Only  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.  

Terms and Conditions  
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.  

Your Consent  
By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.  

Changes to our Privacy Policy  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.  

Contacting Us  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. Or You may contact us form.  

http://goboom.search4i.com

Address :  
4th Floor, Arth Complex,  
B/h L. G. Shoppe, Mithakhali 6 Roads,  
Ahmedabad, India - 380009
